UNITED UNIVERSITY PROFESSIONS (UUP) RECORDS (APAP039) 1964-2000
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subgroup IV: Office of the Secretary, 1968-1999; 6; 61.73
  - Series 3: Chapters, 1968-1996; 6.3; 17.0
    - Subseries 3.3 - Chapter Files [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996; 6.3.3; 14.66
      - Maritime-SPA Newsletter [RESTRICTED], March 1971 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 20)
      - Maritime College-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], 1978-1986 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 21)
      - Morrisville [RESTRICTED], February 1971-December 1981 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 22)
      - Morrisville [RESTRICTED], February 1982-May 1988 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 23)
      - Morrisville [RESTRICTED], February 1989-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 24)
      - Morrisville-SPA Newsletter [RESTRICTED], January 1972; October 1973 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 25)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], November 1970-February 1979 (Box IV.3.3.9, Folder 26)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], March 1979-December 1980 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 1)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], January 1981-November 1981 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 2)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], December 1981-June 1982 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 3)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], July 1982-January 1983 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 4)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], February 1983-March 1984 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 5)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], April 1984-November 1985 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 6)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], December 1985-July 1988 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 7)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], September 1988-October 1990 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 8)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], December 1990-May 1993 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 9)
      - New Paltz-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], October 1977-November/December 1981 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 10)
      - New Paltz-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], January 1982-October/November 1984 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 11)
      - New Paltz-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], December 1984-May 1988 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 12)
      - New York State Theater Institute [RESTRICTED], December 1991-July 1992 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 13)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], January 1971-November 1977 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 14)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], June 1978-May 1982 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 15)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], July 1982-March 1984 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 16)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], May 1984-August 1988 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 17)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], October 1988-April 1991; February 1992-February 22, 1993 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 18)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1993-May 1993 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 19)
      - Old Westbury-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978; 1980-1981 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 20)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], February 1971-October 1984 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 21)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], February 1975-February 1982 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 22)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], March 1982-June 1985 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 23)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], August 1985-April 1987 (Box IV.3.3.10, Folder 24)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], May 1987-October 1988 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 1)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], February 1989-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 2)
      - Oneonta-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], October 1974-March 1988 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 3)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], July 1977-February 1983 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 4)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], March 1983-August 1986 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 5)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], September 1986-April 1992 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 6)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], April 1992-August 1992 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 7)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], August 1992-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 8)
      - Optometry, College of-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], January 1978-October 1984 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 9)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], November 1970-April 1974 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 10)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], May 1974-December 1977 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 11)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], January 1978-December 1981 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 12)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], February 1982-May 1983 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 13)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], June 1983-December 1985 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 14)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], January 1986-June 1986 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 15)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], August 1986-December 1987 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 16)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], November 1988-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 17)
      - Oswego-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], ca. April 1974-July 1975; November 1981-May 1989 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 18)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], February 1971-December 1974 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 19)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], January 1975-June 1981 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 20)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], July 1981-April 1982 (Box IV.3.3.11, Folder 21)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], May 1982-March 1983 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 1)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], April 1983-October 1984 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 2)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], November 1984-December 1986 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 3)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], January 1987-July 1988 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 4)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], September 1988-September 1989 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 5)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], November 1989-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 6)
      - Plattsburgh-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], January 1974; 1978-1988 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 7)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], October 1971-November 1977 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 8)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], January 1978-January 1983 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 9)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], February 1983-December 1985 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 10)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], January 1986-June 1988 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 11)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], September 1988-August 1989 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 12)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], October 1989-November 1991; April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 13)
      - Potsdam-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], December 1973-April 1975; 1978-1985 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 14)
      - Potsdam-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], 1986-May 1988 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 15)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], February 1971-December 1977 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 16)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], January 1978-December 1982 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 17)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], June 1983-July 1987 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 18)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], August 1987-August 1988 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 19)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], February 1988-October 1990 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 20)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], April 1991-May 1992; May 1993 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 21)
      - Purchase-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], ca. 1976?; October 1978-September 1981(?) (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 22)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], January 1971-April 1976 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 23)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], September 1976-December 1977 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 24)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], January 1978-October 1979 (Box IV.3.3.12, Folder 25)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], November 1979-July 1982 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 1)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], August 1982-December 1982 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 2)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], January 1983-May 1984 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 3)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], June 1984-January 1985 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 4)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], February 1985-July 1986 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 5)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], August 1986-April 1987 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 6)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], May 1987-April 1988 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 7)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], September 1988-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 8)
      - Stony Brook-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], ca. December 1974; October 1977-February 1988 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 9)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], April 1971-July 1975 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 10)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], September 1976-November 1979 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 11)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], December 1979-June 1981 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 12)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], July 1981-April 1984 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 13)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], May 1984-March 1988 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 14)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], September 1988-April 1993 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 15)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], January 1978-May 1989 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 16)
      - Upstate Medical Center (Syracuse) [RESTRICTED], June 1971-May 1981 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 17)
      - Upstate Medical Center (Syracuse) [RESTRICTED], June 1981-September 1982 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 18)
      - Upstate Medical Center (Syracuse) [RESTRICTED], October 1982-February 1985 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 19)
      - Upstate Medical Center/Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], March 1985-December 1987 (Box IV.3.3.13, Folder 20)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], January 1988-June 1989 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 1)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], October 1989-February 1990 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 2)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], March 1990-December 1992 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 3)
      - Upstate Medical Center (Syracuse)-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], April 1978-October 1978; December 1980-Fall 1983 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 4)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], September 1975-November 1977 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 5)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], November 1978-May 1982 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 6)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], June 1982-May 1988 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 7)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], November 1988-April 1991; September 1992-May 1993 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 8)
      - Utica/Rome-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], February 1980-November 1987 (Box IV.3.3.14, Folder 9)
      - Albany [RESTRICTED], September 1993-February 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 2)
      - Alfred [RESTRICTED], October 1993-March 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 3)
      - Binghamton [RESTRICTED], June 1993-December 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 4)
      - Brockport [RESTRICTED], October 1993-May 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 5)
      - Brooklyn Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], June 1993-August 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 6)
      - Brooklyn Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], August 1994-October 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 7)
      - Brooklyn Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], November 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 8)
      - SUNY Buffalo [RESTRICTED], July 1993-November 1993 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 9)
      - SUNY Buffalo [RESTRICTED], December 1993-December 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 10)
      - SUNY Buffalo [RESTRICTED], May 1996-July 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 11)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], June 1993-April 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 12)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], May 1994-December 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 13)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], December 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 14)
      - Buffalo State University College [RESTRICTED], August 1993-April 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 12)
      - Canton [RESTRICTED], June 1993-July 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 16)
      - Cobleskill [RESTRICTED], June 1993-February 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 17)
      - Cortland [RESTRICTED], June 1993-March 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 18)
      - Delhi [RESTRICTED], March 1994; February 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 19)
      - Empire State College [RESTRICTED], February 1994-July 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 20)
      - Environmental Science and Forestry [RESTRICTED], February 1995-March 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 21)
      - Farmingdale [RESTRICTED], June 1993-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 22)
      - Fredonia [RESTRICTED], June 1993-March 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 23)
      - Geneseo [RESTRICTED], February 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 24)
      - Maritime [RESTRICTED], October 1993-February 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 25)
      - Morrisville [RESTRICTED], December 1993-December 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 26)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], October 1993-August 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 27)
      - New York State Theater Institute [RESTRICTED], November 1993-June 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 28)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], March 1994-May 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 29)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], February 1995-July 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 30)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], June 1993-June 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 31)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], June 1993-February 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 32)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], March 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 33)
      - Oswego Election Challenge [RESTRICTED], December 1993-March 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 34)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], June 1993-November 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 35)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], June 1993-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 36)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], January 1994-February 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 37)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], July 1993-November 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15, Folder 38)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], July 1993-June 1994 (Box IV.3.3.16, Folder 1)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], July 1994-August 1994 (Box IV.3.3.16, Folder 2)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], August 1994-August 1995 (Box IV.3.3.16, Folder 3)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], June 1993-December 1994 (Box IV.3.3.16, Folder 4)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box IV.3.3.16, Folder 5)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], February 1995 (Box IV.3.3.16, Folder 6)
  - Series 4: Committees, Task Forces, and Working Groups [RESTRICTED], 1978 February-1993 May; 6.4; 12.0
    The records in this series document, to varying degrees, the activities of UUP's standing committees, ad hoc committees, joint labor-management committees, task forces, and working groups. Included for most committees are the administrative correspondence created at UUP's administrative office setting up meetings, obtaining approval from the Governor's Office of Employee Relations for organizational leave time for meeting attendees, and confirming committee appointments. Lists of committee members are also frequently included.
    The substantive work of each committee is documented by meeting agendas and minutes; the materials, such as third-party reports, distributed to committee members for their use in preparing for committee meetings; correspondence between UUP's President and the committee chairperson; and correspondence from UUP's officers and the committee chairperson to the committee as a whole. The records for joint labor-management committees include reports and correspondence prepared by the state with regard to the committee, as well as communications between only UUP's participants on those committees. If a formal report was at some point prepared by a committee or task force, drafts of the report are often included in that committee's or task force's records. Finally, the reports made by the committee chairperson to Delegate Assemblies are occasionally included in this series. (Committee chairperson reports are also found in the Delegate Assembly records in Series 2 of this Subgroup.)
    As of February 2001, UUP's standing committees are: Retired Membership, Affirmative Action, Elections and Credentials, Finance, Grievance, Legislation, Membership, Negotiations, Part-Time Concerns, Solidarity, and Women's Rights and Concerns. Over the years, UUP's ad hoc committees, task forces, and working groups have addressed a variety of issues, particularly in the area of higher education and improving SUNY (for example, the Student Retention and Recruitment Committee, the Public Education Committee, the Undergraduate Education Task Force, the Teacher Education Task Force, the University Development Committee, and the Excellence Committee). Issues of concern to particular segments of UUP's bargaining unit have also been addressed (for example, the Colleges of Technology Task Force, the Health Science Center Concerns Committee, and the Nursing Profession Work Group). Joint labor-management committees have addressed safety and health issues, child care, health benefits, professional study leaves, employee assistance programs, salary disparities, and providing retraining and re-education opportunities for retrenched employees. Finally, some of UUP's committees have focused on improving UUP and its operations such as the Constitutional Study Committee, the Computer Technology Committee, and the Re-Imagine UUP Committee.
    Committee-specific materials include election result reports and correspondence on possible election irregularities for the Elections and Credentials Committee; financial summaries and the report of the treasurer, and chapter budget requests and approval requests for extraordinary expenditures for the Finance Committee; chapter responses to a survey on membership and membership recruitment activities in 1982 for the Membership Committee; proposed legislation and state budgets for the Legislation Committee; and studies on indoor air pollution and other workplace health concerns for the Safety and Health Committee. There is some overlap between the records of the Membership Committee and Retired Membership Committee because correspondence were occasionally addressed to both groups, and they deal with an overlapping area of interest. The files for the Negotiations Committee has correspondence, appointment letters, and meeting information for UUP's Negotiations Team and its Ad Hoc Advisory Committee for Negotiations, occasional negotiations bulletins and responses to members on issues of concern for negotiations, and multiple copies of lists of committee and team members as well as some attendance lists for negotiations meetings and workshops. Grievance committee records include reports to the president recommending the continued pursuit or the abandonment of specific grievances. Background materials for some of the applications submitted to the Legal Defense Fund Committee are included with the records of that committee.
    The amount of materials available for each committee, task force, and working group, and the degree of organization of those materials, varies. The records that make up this series were primarily taken from the main committee records maintained by UUP's statewide secretary. Frequently, however, additional folders for specific committees were encountered during processing and incorporated into this series. Except in a few instances when the additional materials were retained separately because the identity of the individual maintaining the records was known, the new materials were interfiled in chronological order into the main committee files, which were themselves organized, to the extent possible, into chronological order during processing. The records for the Legislation Committee during the 1980s were in particular disarray and it was only possible to put them in rough chronological order. Throughout this series, undated materials were kept near their original location but due to the sometimes widely varying dates of the documents found on either side of undated documents, some undated materials may not be correctly located by date. The names of a few committees and task forces have changed over the years, however for the most part just one name is used for each committee in the folder list for this series.
    Materials related to committee work during the mid-1970s can also be found in the SPA/UUP Administrative Office General Files in Series 2 of Subgroup II, usually under the name of the topic that each committee dealt with rather than the committee name itself (i.e., Legislation or Membership rather than Legislation Committee or Membership Committee). Committee files for 1975-1981 are also located in Subgroup III, Subseries 3.1, Wakshull Administration, Subject Files. Finally, the project and subject files in Series 5 of Subgroup III include materials relating to the work of some committees, task forces, and working groups during the Reilly presidency from May 1987 to May 1993.
    - Academic Research and Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 September-1993 April (Box IV.4.1, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1981 May (Box IV.4.1, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1981 June-1982 March (Box IV.4.1, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982 April-1983 November (Box IV.4.1, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983 December-1985 October (Box IV.4.1, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 November-1986 December 05 (Box IV.4.1, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 December 08-1987 March (Box IV.4.1, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 April-1987 July (Box IV.4.1, Folder 8)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1989 May (Box IV.4.1, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June-1992 December (Box IV.4.1, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action Joint Labor/Management Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 August-1989 March (Box IV.4.1, Folder 11)
    - Affirmative Action Committee (Joint Labor/Management) minutes and leave grant applications [RESTRICTED], 85-88 contract; 3 folders (Box IV.4.1, Folder 12-14)
    - Affirmative Action Committee-Cultural Diversity Steering Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June (Box IV.4.1, Folder 15)
    - AIDS Work Group reference materials [RESTRICTED], 1986-1989 (Box IV.4.1, Folder 16)
    - AIDS Work Group [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1989 January (Box IV.4.1, Folder 17)
    - Archives Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1991 May (Box IV.4.1, Folder 18)
    - Career Development Committee (Joint Labor-Management/Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees) [RESTRICTED], 1979 July-1980 May (Box IV.4.1, Folder 19)
    - Career Development Committee (Joint Labor-Management/Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees) [RESTRICTED], 1980 September-1982 March (Box IV.4.1, Folder 20)
    - Chapter Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1988 February; 1990 March-1991 September; 1992 November-1993 April (Box IV.4.1, Folder 21)
    - Chapter Release Time (Article 11.6) Subcommittee (Chapter Development Committee) [RESTRICTED], 1985 December-1991 March (Box IV.4.1, Folder 22)
    - Child Care Advisory Committee, New York State Labor/Management [RESTRICTED], 1987 November-1993 April (Box IV.4.1, Folder 23)
    - Clinical Practice Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1986 July-1987 January (Box IV.4.2, Folder 1)
    - Clinical Practice Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1987 February-1988 March (Box IV.4.2, Folder 2)
    - Clinical Practice Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1990 October (Box IV.4.2, Folder 3)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women, Committee on [RESTRICTED], 1981 July-1982 September (Box IV.4.2, Folder 4)
    - Colleges of Technology, Task Force on [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box IV.4.2, Folder 5)
    - Computer Technology Committee (T. Matthews, Treasurer, file) [RESTRICTED], 1984 July-1988 June (Box IV.4.2, Folder 6)
    - Computer Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1985 September (Box IV.4.2, Folder 7)
    - Computer Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 October-1989 June (Box IV.4.2, Folder 8)
    - Computer Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1993 March (Box IV.4.2, Folder 9)
    - Constitutional Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1979 February (Box IV.4.2, Folder 10)
    - Constitution Study Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 August-1988 December (Box IV.4.2, Folder 11)